Numbers, some positioning,
technology
thing in terms of results. Accenture's
results came and the guidance they gave is a
very similar model. You are a lot of
firefighters, it's a company which outsources a lot of work
for major retail, online help
players in North America and Europe.
Commentary from Accenture shows
that the growth momentum is slowing down. So, I
think we can buy, we can build volume
and constant currency revenue
growth. This is exhausting.
Secondly, I think in terms of the margin
profile, it's self-margin ODI thing, it may be
collected.
Whatever wages are there, we may build that
and the outsourcing expenses
may come down. Travel rental expenses and
steel remaining elevated and because of this, the
margin profile may be a little better.
Having said that, the third very
important aspect is the management
commentary or follow-up. Everyone knows that it's
Christmas holidays, all these will definitely have an impact on
Q3 numbers, but my opinion.
Senses that if a slowdown
in this will happen and if this wiper is
lost, will the management commentary
and guidance change in the second quarter, i.e. the
first quarter of the next
financial year? If this happens, then the
valuations at which this company is still trading may
see a little more contraction. So,
we believe that
its underperformance will continue. I
think all the factors,
what is my today's funda? Let me tell you,
ICICI General is quite liking it.
Two-three things are happening for this company. The
losses that we have seen are very
important. Generally,
for an insurance company, this is not a big deal. We are making every
effort to reduce them in the second half. And
when will this happen significantly? You will see a significant reduction in losses in the second half of 2023 and
first half of 2024,
which will
prove Aarohi significantly. Secondly, I
think Vijendra Products, if you
look at the portfolio of Group Health, it
seems constructive. The benefits are there for
Retail Health.  Banks have become
Sharan, Adar Vice C will definitely add retail
health going forward and motor
insurance is
direct, here the premium prop is getting quite good, we are
expecting and the
loss that I was talking about, both for group, I think very very
constructive on reported
Arohi, the third is the interested scenario, when you
look at the interest rate, the interested
region will actually help
investment returns, ICICI General Care, those who
follow the growth and profitability strategies of general, will see a good increase in the middle,
45%, which is the crop business, we
want to keep it only up to 5%, which is above the white
on drive
sheet and hence the combined ratio is
above 105%, solving series 2.47 times and those who are
expecting Arohi,
clearly following 70%, will see a good
improvement in it in the second half,
so we think that with this you
can remember
clear stock,
we are moving towards a very good closing,
now in such a situation  We can take fundamental calls,
Mahesh ji, if you yourself
are not comfortable, then please tell us some good calls from your technical research
team, whom you repeatedly bring in,
please, there is a
short top call going on, yes,
our filter is in the market data, which I
repeatedly mention, new high rate 9,
you will see decline in that, these general insurance
less and without
GIC, this is something which I think can
give a mutual short of return,
two-three things are happening, like we had
said for ICICI General also, I think the
rates for reinsurance have become
quite competitive, losses have come
down significantly and GST is
specifically in the centre and as much as I
think, one problem has been
seen in the first, both the terms and conditions of cross
premium sir, which is called cross written direct
premium, you can mop, be it on fire, on haul,
on cargo, thoughts show
strong recovery, secondly, you and raw
special should also be good, when should the
combined ratio be solvin series  And it is
good for Shahrukh including GIC. But I was
looking at two things. First
thing, I think the overall insurance segment, i.e.
insurance market, should give a growth of 7 to 8
percent in the next two to
three years. Secondly, I think
in the last budget, the government gave shoulder bonds as a
substitute for bank guarantees. The insurance support to non-life
player
companies,
I think this budget will probably go
towards this because insurance and
infrastructure projects which
should be supported will be pretty much in turn to the
general elections. I think
secondly, Ayushman Bharat Digital Health had an
allocation of 1600 crores for 5
years. So, for the healthcare space today, the
government will go all out. Special
position can be given which can help the non-life
insurance sector a lot. When
we talk about group health insurance,
I think GIC will be in short in the budget space from
here.